MUKUL SAINI

WEB DEVELOPER GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT

- +91 8769506494
- thisismemukul@gmail.com
- in LinkenIn
- Github
- Be Behance

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership/Team Player
- Problem Solving
- Quick Learner
- Attention to detail

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi

EDUCATION

POORNIMA INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, JAIPUR(RAJ)

Aug 2019 - Present | Pursuing B-tech in Computer Science Engineering.

SVM Public School

2018 - 2019 12th Standard | PCM

ABOUT ME

Full-Stack Developer with 3+ years of experience leading both front-end with the ability to perform well in team/individual. Skilled in writing applications interface code via Javascript and ReactJS with MVC architecture. I build websites and graphics that delight and inform.

EXPERIENCE

E-CELL, IIT BOMBAY

Web Coordinator · Internship Worked on a MERN Stack Project as a leader, with my team.

April 2021 - Sep 2021 · 6 mos

CREATIVE GEEK STUDIO

Front-End Developer Video Editor | Animator

Build frontend for different websites, using REACT and MUI. And made animated videos using After Effects.

Jan 2021- Mar 2021

DIGIVENTRY MARKETING

Graphic & Motion Designer
I created logos, posters, video edit,
graphic works with Adobe softwares.
April 2021 - Jun 2021 · 3 mos

THE WEBCONIX

Graphic & Motion Designer I created posters, video edit, and other graphic works.

Aug 2020- April 2021

PROJECTS

T-Shirt Hub

- A MERN Stack e-commerce Project.
- With a stripe and brain-tree payment gateway
- MVC architecture Based.

NODE MOVIE SEARCH API WEB APP

- Users can Search Lists of Movies and Series based on keywords.
- Made with OMDB API with Node and Express.

YELP CAMP AND CHEAPCODE

 These are the Node Js projects in which we can create camparounds and blog posts respectively

COVID RESOURCES WEB APP

 This web app provides and donates medical supplies.

RENTWEB E-COMMERCE

 This is an online product renting website made with PHP/MySQL.

TECH SKILLS

- Front-end Development: ReactJS, MUI, JavaScript
- Back-end Development: JavaScript, Nodeis, Express
- Databases: MongoDB,MySQL
- Graphic Designing: Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop
- UI/UX Design: Adobe XD, Figma
- Video Editing: Adobe After Effects, Media Encoder
- Language: C, C++, Java
- Operating System: Linux, Windows, Mac
- Git & GitHub